Guide to the Gordon F. Madding Collection, 1840-1897. [photostats].
Department of Special Collections
Gordon F. Madding Collection,
1840-1897. [photostats].
Special Collections M0030
Madding, Gordon F.
1 folder
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Gift of Dr. Gordon F. Madding, 1960.
Abstract
Photostat. [s.1.: s.n., 19--] 25 p.
Originals held by George F. Madding.
Scope and Content
Contains photostats of letters written by authors of the Victorian era in England, including Charles Dickens, Wilkie Collins, A. Tennyson Dickens, John Forester, G. Hagarty, Leigh Hunt and T. B. Macaulay.
Container List
- Wilkie Collins 1858 Apr. 26to [unidentified]
- A. Tennyson Dickens [18--] Nov. 5to Wm. G. Wilkins
- John Forester 1860 Aug. 22to Dixon
- John Forester 1874 Jan. 12to [unidentified]
- William Forester [1854]to Paxton
- Charles Dickens 1852 Jan. 1to [Joseph Janion]
- Charles Dickens 1852 [July 10]to John Knowles
- Charles Dickens 1865to "Dear Frederick"
- Charles Dickens 1869to "Dear Dolf"
- Charles Dickens 1870to Mr. Gardner (incomplete)
- G. Hogarty 1897to Miss Rockwell
- Leigh Hunt [18--] June 23to Knight
- [W.R.] Macauley 1840to T.B. Macauley with T.B. Macauley's signature